Downloaded from
HQCINEMAS.COM
Official HQCINEMAS movies site:
Good afternoon.
Why are you here?
Sorry, my dear.
Give me the bag.
Hey! Give him the bag.
I'm in trouble.
Please.
Fight!
Ah ah
London, this guy can't do it.
I can do it.
Ahn ahn
Money! Money!
- This is the major one.
- This one wants to travel to America.
- Leave it
- What?
She'll probably need it.
We shouldn't throw it away.
Ify! Use your brain!
Use your head!
This could get us in trouble.
Are you the boss?
I am the boss.
No! I am the boss.
You who was afraid of that fat woman?
My father was a great king,
You have to listen to what I say.
Okay then,
If you are the boss,
Teni is my girl.
Ahhh
What is it with you guys and this girl?
You're the boss.
Thanks for having my back there.
That woman almost shit her pants.
You're my blood.
No one messes with my blood.
- How about me?
- Chill... You're our bro.
Street brothers for life.
Street brothers forever.
Swear on your life!
Eww!
Am I not a girl?
- Well done.
- Honestly.
PND party,
They want 15 local governments
To win in the upcoming state primaries.
That's easy, I swear.
You know we got this.
KZ
I would like you to give Akinwale
and I a few minutes of privacy.
Chill out.
Baba,
I am tired of this street life, Baba.
Honestly.
I have gathered quite a bit of money.
Baba.
I am ready to start a new business.
Akinwale.
I know that you are still a young man
But that does not mean
you should not be wise.
Listen,
don't be deceived by anyone.
Look,
Let me tell you,
To the kind of life that every aspiring,
young Isale Eko boy is dreaming of.
Listen, even Kazeem can't match you.
You better wise up!
What is wrong with you?
Can you imagine that?
Take it easy.
Thank you.
Madam.
I'm sorry.
You said your bag was stolen.
If this happened in Isale Eko,
like you said, then relax.
Yes, sir.
Terrible!
Here's the bag. We found it.
That's him! That's him!
Woman, relax!
I'm sorry, sir
Get up.
Child of God.
What's your name?
There were two of them, sir.
The other one ran...
Where's your friend?!
What? I'll slap you so hard you'll...
Terrible
Baba.
It was just me, sir.
My name is Akande...
Really? Obalola?
How is that?
Who is your father?
Are you the son of a dead King?
Yes, sir.
- You're Ogunmola's son?
- Yes, sir.
Come closer.
Can't be true.
You are your father's son.
Look,
You know what we'll do?
You see,
You'll return the bag to her
because you don't bring harm
to your own people.
You understand?
Yes, Sir.
But...
she has gone to the cops.
Madam,
The police?
I just had to formally report
my missing passport.
Enough! No need to explain at all.
You see the police you reported to?
You'll go back to them
and they will help you
find your missing bag.
Oh! I have upset you?
Terrible!
Obalola!
Teni.
Teniola!
Put your head back in!
Obalola!
Obasco!
Smart boy.
You've made a lot of money today.
Sir?
You can’t play smart with me…
I’ll just throw you a punch
Look at me.
I know you didn’t steal the bag alone.
You’re just protecting your friend, right?
Omo aiye never brings harm to his own.
So, what police station did
you see her enter?
So, how did you know
she went to the police?
Obasco!
You’re no ordinary boy.
I see now that
you’re truly your fathers son.
- Yes, sir.
- Wonderful...
but I need you to listen.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, sir.
I appreciate it.
What?
Thank you.
Well played boy.
If you need anything,
ask for Ninalowo on Ricca street.
- Ricca Street?
- Yes.
That's where Teni lives.
Kazeem’s daughter?
I noticed you staring at her.
They live next door.
Thank you, sir.
What are you doing here?!
Take your evil money and leave my son!
Madam, I was just talk…
Don't speak to me!
I don’t want to hear your voice!
What did I do to you this child?
Why do you want to ruin me?
But I won’t let you!
I won’t let the devil take your soul!
Do you hear me?
You know what?
We are going to the aladura!
No! Mummy please!
- Don’t let me slap you! Let’s go!
- Mummy please!
Mummy please!
My darling…
You know I’m doing all this for you.
I'm doing it so the evil spirits
in you can leave.
So I can rest knowing you will
live long and be prosperous.
Be strong...
The pain shows that God is working in you.
It is a sign that the battle is won.
Obalola,
I wasn’t expecting you so soon.
I’m looking for a place to stay.
Who did this to you?
Come… Come in
Do we have a guest?
We have a son.
Obalola, come in.
Obasco,
All of this is yours.
I want you to sleep well tonight.
Don't worry about anything.
We'll talk tomorrow. All right?
Smart boy.
Obalola!
Obalola.
Oba.
- Bring my son.
- What child?
Evil woman! How do you treat
your own child like that?
Go in and bring my son.
Face me. Leave the small boy alone.
- Who's making all that noise?
- What are you going to do?
Princess, come in. Come in.
- Look, bring me my child.
- What child?
I know you’re hiding him,
so just go in and bring him to…
Oh, my Akani, My darling. Thank God.
Come, come let’s go.
I’m not leaving.
Leave these evil people, let’s go home!
You have to leave the boy
The boy says he’s not leaving.
I dare you to step a foot in this house!
You are not leaving.
It is not a curse.
You see this path your father took
this is the same path your father took
with these evil people,
these criminals...
This is the same path you want to follow.
This path?
Will lead to your death.
Enough!
Never will you speak to this boy
in that way again!
Have you ever been to a house like this?
This is where rich and
important people live.
One day,
we would live in a place like this.
They don’t have two heads, right?
Akinwale
How are you?
You wait here.
I'll be back.
Obasco!
Oba!
I want you to wait for me in the car.
Whatever you do, don't leave this car.
They didn’t tell me anything!
Stop screaming.
- Please.
- Shhhh.
Listen,
I can keep cutting you from now
till the sun comes up.
I won’t even get bored.
Listen, you will pray for death
but you won't find it.
You won't die till I'm ready to kill you.
My ear!
Obalola!
I told you to wait in the car!
Nino, you brought a child here.
I couldn't leave him alone at home.
It's all good.
Looks like the kid
has the stomach for this.
Holding a knife to that child's neck?
The dead king’s son.
The apple doesn’t fall far from the tree.
Look, he was born for this life.
No one is born for this life.
It's been 7 days...
No one one has seen her.
We have given the police all our savings,
but they are too scared
to go and search that place.
Please help me.
That man promised her
that he will take her to London,
But we have heard that he uses
people to smuggle drugs.
Please help me.
You should have come to me earlier.
I didn’t know better.
I know London very well.
If your daughter is with him,
I'll get her out.
London!
Where are you?!
Who’s the mad man
barking like a dog in my club?
You're talking to Ninalowo
The girl in this picture,
she's my child, and I heard you have her.
Yes, she is here.
The girl in the picture
and all the other girls here,
they’re all bought and paid for.
Not this girl.
Listen
You can look out your windows
if you please,
I came with an army.
I either leave with the girl,
or we all die here tonight.
- Arrow.
- Baba.
Go get the whore so these
bastards can get the hell out of here.
London... till we meet again
You know what that means, right?
Get out of my club!
and you, knockoff white man.
Fuck shit up.
You?
So you don't believe me?
Never!
For me?
Look at me, Look at me.
Obasco!
Are you enjoying your food?
Well done. I’ll see you later.
Yes Sir
Smart child.
Goodbye.
Take it easy.
Nice guy.
Mama, we protect you.
- Omo ibo, you are back.
- Mama, we protect you.
You don't have...
Anyone, just give it to me.
What is it?!
Money, money, money every time!
- Pay up.
- You like money.
Hey, look who it is.
- Mummy.
- Ify.
Mummy.
What did you just do?
Ify Collector!
How are you?
- What?
- That's Kazeem.
Don't let him hear you call me that.
That was in his time.
This is your own time now.
You’re the boss now.
Let me give you some corn?
Leave the corn,
I’m here for Kazeem’s money.
- Really? How are you?
- Yes, mummy. I'm fine.
Mama Nkechi… come…
This is Mama Nkechi
Yes.
She doesn't have the money for this month.
Ha!
Relax,
she will pay you next month.
I guarantee you.
I know but Kazeem
doesn't want to hear stories.
The elections are here and
he's not being merciful.
That man is too greedy.
Mummy, be careful what you say.
The walls have ears.
But it's true...
if he and Olorogun collect everything,
What will the rest of us eat?
But Kazeem provides protection.
What protection?!
My son protects me!
You will protect me. Ify the collector.
Collector, protector!
- Mummy, I know what you're doing...
- It is working...
Where is Wemimo?
Aren't these Kazeem's boys?
There's trouble!
Lunatics!
Wemimo,
If you don't come out right away,
I'll blow your head off.
Please. My brother, please.
Brother Wemimo, hope all is well.
Don't you dare!
Everything is fine.
Bring the money.
Count it! Is it complete?
- It is complete.
- That's a good boy.
How much?
Do you want to be unfortunate?
Get out of the car!
I'll kill you.
Please have mercy. It was the devil
When you meet the devil,
you can explain that to him.
What's up?
Please, have mercy.
- Alaye.
- Eruku.
Please, have mercy
Please… please
I’m finished!
We’ve had enough.
We’re done. We don’t want you any longer.
This is not a monarchy.
Why can’t they use their children?
They keep their kids abroad.
Why?
She’s all talk. Don't be bothered.
We own the streets.
Wemimo, Wemimo!
Is that you?
How are you?
Come on… don’t be sacred.
Relax, feel at home.
Come sit.
Sit.
Wemimo. Wemimo. Relax.
Come closer. Don’t be shy.
You cannot steal from my collections.
And then you suddenly lose your voice.
Actually, sir...
It was a miscalculation...
- Really?
- Yes, sir.
A miscalculation?
You know what?
I'm inclined to believe you.
A miscalculation
Yes, sir.
But you know I have eyes and ears
everywhere.
Mr. Man, go inside!
Wemimo, Wemimo!
I’m finished!
How’s it going?
- Have they come for their meat?
- No they haven't.
They haven’t come.
Come this way!
Please, sir.
Please.
- Wemimo.
- Sir.
Do you still maintain
that it was a miscalculation?
I’ll confess.
- I did it.
- You did it?
I did it.
But, sir, it wasn't me.
It was an evil spirit. It was madness.
An evil spirit.
A miscalculation…
I'm a butcher's son.
I have been butchering both animals
and humans since I was a child.
Next time when someone
sends you to steal from me.
You either kill them yourselves,
Or...
In the words of Jesus Christ,
bring them to me.
Obasco!
Sir.
Well done.
Your friend is coming back.
- Teni?
- Yes.
You see, this election is
going to get really tough.
It will get really tough.
I told her not to come home
but the girl is too stubborn.
That's Teni.
I’ve found her a job on the Island,
a friend of mine offered her a job.
So I've bought her a flat.
But...
I want you to be her personal bodyguard
and her security person.
Nothing can happen to Teni,
she's all I have.
Nothing will happen to her.
I trust you.
That's why I chose you.
Take this.
Who should I give it to?
It’s yours.
For what?
Use it to take care of yourself.
This is too much.
Come on.
You’re like a son to me.
Ninalowo’s son is my son.
So if I don’t take care of you, who will?
Obasco!
Fifty thousand Naira.
I just need to raise the funds.
I hear you want to talk?
- That's right.
- Go on.
I have a bulk shipment of coke and you’re
the only one I trust to deal with it.
Have you guys lost your minds?!
In my hood?!
In my hood!
- Have you lost your minds?
- Kashope!
- Calm down.
- Oba!
Take my name out of your mouth.
- Calm down!
- Have you lost your mind?
It seems you have lost your mind!
I'll hit you with...
Hands up!
Calm down.
Bringing a gun to a knife fight?
Relax!
Bar man, for the damage…
I dare you to try me.
Calm down! What if you shoot and miss?!
You’ll just die for nothing. Try me.
See his head like a goat's head.
Why don't you say it in Yoruba? Bastard.
He said your head looks
like that of a goat.
Filthy witch!
Demon!
- I’ll smash your head in.
- I’ll mess you up!
We should have beaten Kashope.
He’s such an idiot!
Your house or your mother’s house?
She won’t do anything…
Ifeanyi!
Ifeanyi, so you’re here.
Look at this Bastard.
I’ve been looking everywhere for you.
Who is this?
You better run.
He’ll get you pregnant then disappear!
Ifeanyi, you!
You did this to me, Ifeanyi
What exactly do you want to explain?
How you didn't show up at the hospital?
You then sent your stupid friend
to bring me 50,000 Naira.
Worthless money. 50,000 Naira.
How dare you?!
I was scared. A baby is a lot.
A baby is a lot?
Blessing!
What sort of rubbish talk is that?
Do you know where I live?
Do you know where I sleep?
Do you know where your child...
Leave me alone!
My landlord kicked me and your baby out.
I sIept in the streets for two days.
It won't be well with you.
Blessing look at me. Calm down
Take us to where you're staying.
You're moving out tonight.
Ify will do right by you.
Even if I have to break his head.
Do you hear me?
I swear to God, I will.
To God who made me.
Why didn’t you swear in Satan’s name.
You stupid idiot.
No need to kick a man
when he’s already down.
I hope this doesn't
land you in trouble someday.
Nonsense person.
My boy! My Boy!
Just look at how handsome my boy is.
Look at his perfect little nose!
We will name him
after your father,
Ikechukwu David.
Yes! Just like his father!
Like his mother too.
So, you see my boy...
He will cause problems.
Listen, babe...
Once my music blows up,
I’m going to marry you.
Lies!
- See, I swear...
- Shut up over there and stop swearing!
Even your mum knows you're lying.
Guys, I'll never forget what
you guys did for me this night.
- Are you teasing me?
- I'm not.
Street brothers for life.
That's disgusting!
Obalola!
Teni.
Are you going to let go of each other?
Are you bound?
They’re acting like in an Indian film.
Is this really you?
It’s been ten years.
Are you sure you went to America?
Where’s the accent?
What silly accent?
I'm just an Isale Eko girl.
- Ebun!
- Eruku!
I’m loyal!
You’re so local!
Are you sure you went to the real America?
I’m local and proud!
Igbo boy!
My crush.
- My sugar Banana.
- My boo.
My baby boo boo.
Igbo boy.
- Igbo boy.
- My boo.
What are you wearing?
He’s a baby daddy now.
What happened?
I have so much to tell you, you won’t
believe what happened with this boy.
Obasco!
Sir.
Tenilola.
Look who is talking.
Don't you know you are all grown up too.
- Good morning.
- Oba.
Good morning. How are you?
Remember the house I told you
I bought for Teni?
That’s where you’ll take her.
I’ve sent you the address.
I have it.
She’s the apple of my eye.
- Do you hear me?
- I’ll take care of her.
I trust you.
Bye, daddy.
The both of you are going to
run an errand for me.
Come on, let’s go!
Igbo boy… You’re with me.
Let's go.
Yes, Sir.
Why do you always dress like a man?
Why does your mouth stink so bad?
Just because I joke around with you?
Don't do that with me.
You better ask why they call me Terrible.
I’m warning you.
You are probably sleeping with Eleniyan.
So he asked you to join us.
This job we’re going for
isn’t child’s play.
You need to be smart!
Wait…
How many people will live in here?
Don't be silly. I know it's big.
It even has a balcony.
Teni, do you really own this house?
Technically, it’s my dad’s
but he bought it in my name.
It won't be well with the person
that killed my father.
I should go with you!
Who will stay on the look out
if you come with us?
Look, just because the boss
trusts you, doesn’t mean I do.
Let’s move!
Ify, I have some good news for you.
Yes.
Remember that producer you’ve
been wanting to work with?
I’ve spoken to him and he says you should
come and perform for him this weekend.
That's enough. Don't prostrate
whilst you're driving.
Look where you're going.
Thank you, sir.
I won't disappoint you.
You wouldn’t dare.
Panama.
Alaye.
Eleniyan.
Good afternoon, Sir
How are you?
We’re fine, sir.
Boys! Pack up!
You’ve already cut off my hair.
What’s going on?
I’ve been waiting for over 30mins.
You haven’t even done my friction
I said get the fuck out of here!
We’re closed!
Sorry about that, sir.
Now you leave.
I knew my eyes weren’t deceiving me.
It's been 16 years.
But you’re a coward.
We could have met anywhere.
Why would you choose to ambush me here?
Wherever we are is
where the battle is fought.
Or have you forgotten my promise
that we would meet again?
If you weren’t a coward,
we wouldn’t be meeting here.
You know you’re no match for me
so you ambush me here.
Only traitors have something to fear.
If you’ve done nothing,
you have nothing to fear.
Your loyalties are misplaced.
Olorogun will betray you.
And you will betray the hand that fed you?
Tajudeen, for what?
For this ordinary woman?
Someone that is going nowhere?
Isn’t it time Olorogun’s reign ended?
After over 20 years of ruling over Lagos.
His time is up! He should leave.
Such a pity. You have forgotten.
You’ve forgotten that you were
roaming the streets
like a mad man.
High off your mind on all sorts of drugs.
Then Olorogun found you,
took mercy on your wretched soul
and changed your life.
Now you think you can meddle
in the affairs of Lagos?
Shut the fuck up!
Where the fuck are you from anywhere?
You bastard with no pedigree.
I was born here in Lagos Island,
My family house is on Campos street.
Who the hell is your father,
you fucking bastard?!
- Why are you running?
- I'll still get you.
You are running. You are mad.
Pick it up.
It's Pana.
I'll call him back.
I remember the day you
moved into Nino's house.
I remember too.
I was going through so much back then.
But then I saw you…
and my mind felt at ease.
So... you liked me that much?
Are you messing with me?
You knew I liked you.
But you’re ahead now.
I'm sure you met big guys in America.
Guys that went to University,
Not guys like us that didn't
finish secondary school.
None of that really matters.
What education does he have?
Really? What education does he have?
What happened to you?
You used to be all about going to school.
All to what end?
Power is what really matters.
Power.
A million and one people
willing to die
for a cause they know
absolutely nothing about.
Power.
How do you wield this power?
Eruku.
Exactly
Girl, You've changed a lot!
Really? I thought you said
I was the same Teni from Isale Eko
Nah, I was foolish to think that.
You're your father's daughter.
Wait here for Eleniyan.
Ify.
How are you?
Well done.
You impressed me yesterday.
You made me proud.
You held your own as a man should.
Yes, sir.
There’s something I need you to do.
What is that?
You’ve heard the news.
Yes, sir.
So you know we can't have anyone talking.
Sir... I would never.
You?! Oh, I wasn't worried about you.
But... The barber.
I need you to take care of him
I don’t understand, sir.
What don't you understand?
Take care of him.
Make sure he can never utter a word again.
When you’re done, come to the club
so you can perform for the producer.
- Tonight, Sir?
- Of course.
You’re not ready?
No, sir. I’m ready
When you’re done,
come and meet me at the club.
Thank you, sir.
Listen, no need to thank family.
I take care of my own,
and I expect loyalty
in return.
Who is that?
Guy, I've been calling you
since yesterday night.
Where were you?
You want to spoil my door.
I was driving Teni around.
Kazeem killed London.
What?
I swear, the barbershop, the fat guy.
BJ?
Yes. So we get to shop and
I think Kazeem wants a haircut.
Next thing you know, London is reading
a newspaper, one person says something,
and before you know it,
Kazeem just shot the guy.
Maybe Olorogun ordered it.
It’s already on the news.
I'm a Lagosian. I was born here.
Same night he arranges
for me to meet the producer.
Kazeem?
Keep up! Yes, Kazeem.
Calm down!
How can I calm down?
As we were leaving, I saw Kash.
He saw me.
Don't worry, Kash is Ekun's son…
Even though he's a fucking traitor,
Ekun will not touch Nino's son.
And they know you can't kill a Capo...
when you're not mad.
Look lay low till tonight.
We'll go together to the barber.
Will you kill him?
Oba, I talk a lot of shit
but I’ve never killed before...
Calm down! We're not killing anyone.
Unless he's being unreasonable.
We'll convince the barber to leave Lagos.
For his own good.
Then tomorrow morning,
we'll go and see Ekun.
Stop shaking. Take your phone.
- What’s up?
- You should come with us.
To do what?
I’ll bring you something.
Teni, please don’t stay too long.
I've heard you.
Hello Pana.
Where are you? I have eyes on BJ.
Fuck!
Pana, don’t do anything till I get there.
Just wait for me. Wait!
Pana where are you? He’s here!
Really? I’ll be there soon.
Make it fast.
I'll call you.
Teni, get in the car!
Why are you raising your voice at me?
I don’t have time for this,
get in the car now!
Oba,
what's the problem?
What have I done to you?
Not everything is about you Teni.
Well, something is wrong
and instead of sulking around,
let’s talk about it.
Really? You want to talk?
Okay, let’s talk.
Let's talk about how your father
has all of us in the streets,
collecting from everyone,
no matter how little they have,
so you guys can live like kings.
Have you seen how big your flat is?
It’s big enough for 30 people!
You want us to talk right?
Let's talk!
Let's talk about how your father sends
young boys, barely teenagers,
to die everyday on the streets.
For what?!
So your family can have power!
You sit there comfortably in the back
and watch me drive you everyday.
Me, Obalola Akande.
You're okay with me being your driver
and security, right?
I don't have hopes and dreams, right?
My friends... people I love,
who's going to protect them?
Oba...
I didn't ask for this life.
You didn't ask for this life?
Oh, but I did?
Rubbish talk.
Oba!
Risi, is that you?
Did you forget something?
Do you remember my face?
Please.
I've done everything you've asked me to.
Kazeem said I would be a protected man.
Thank you! Thank you very much!
Look, the kind of shit you’re in,
the people looking to kill you,
if you’re ever seen again,
you and everyone you care about
will be hunted down and killed.
I swear to you, I’ll disappear.
You’ll never see me again.
Teni!
Teni! Don't be scared.
Hey, calm the fuck down!
Leave her, take me instead.
Who the fuck are you?!
Touch me one more fucking time,
I'll shoot your head off.
Gift.
Where are you?
They’re calling your name.
Welcome on stage, Panama!
- Panama!
- Pana!
- Where is Panama?
Panama, where are you?
DJ play some music!
Put your gun down or we’ll shoot your guy
Teni, don’t listen!
Sorry.
It’s nothing.
Let me take a look at it.
I'm so sorry.
- I’m so sorry. I’m so stupid.
- Teni...
I should be apologising.
If I hadn’t been talking all that shit,
I wouldn’t have gotten distracted.
If anything had happened to you,
I would have...
Pana!
Ify!
Oba, pick up your fucking phone!
Pana!
Ify!
What do you think they would say?
It’s Gift and Pana you should worry
about, they would so make fun of us.
What is it?
What's the matter?
Oba, say something. What's the matter?
Gift, where’s Pana?
Where were you? Where the fuck were you?!
You were supposed to be with him?
Where the fuck did you go?!
He was all alone.
They killed my son...
When they killed his father,
I didn’t complain,
I accepted it.
Who am I to question God?
Who am I?
But you see...
This one, I will not accept.
I will not accept.
Look at my son’s face! Look at him!
They wanted to cover the coffin
but I refused.
All of you must use your eyes to
see what they did to my son!
My own child.
The God who fights for me.
The God who conquers all my battles.
The God who listens and answers me.
The God who wages war
against those in battle with me.
Arise and fight for me. The time is now!
For all those involved in my son's death!
They shall fall one after the other.
For one scar, 10 men shall fall.
Isale Eko must not know peace.
I said it!
Isale Eko must not know peace
until the wrath of God is felt!
Ifeanyichukwu, show no mercy…
My God... The apple of my eye.
Show no mercy.
Kash!
Ekun!
If you know you're men, come out here.
Come and finish what you started.
I hear a dog barking.
I’m here.
On our turf.
Come and finish what you started.
You’re a fool.
Boys, show no mercy!
I can see you’re ready to meet your maker.
You’re a tough guy, right?
You smell like death.
I’m ready to die,
but I’m taking you with me.
No need for weapons,
I’ll kill you with my bare hands.
Let’s go!
It seems you are unfortunate.
You!
Help me take off my chain.
- You broke my ice!
- You can't stand me.
Bloodclat!
Bruce Lee! You need to calm down!
You godforsaken traitors. How could you?
How could you kill one of Nino's children?
Really?
Where did you hear that I killed him?
You’re going to pretend you didn’t
see Pana outside the barber's shop?
Cowards.
You couldn't get to Kazeem,
so you killed him.
Pana. Harmless Pana.
Are you dumb?
Is your brain empty?
This from you.
Oba, this from you?
When you were a child Nino used
to tell us all how intelligent you were.
That you were smart beyond your years...
Looks like the hot sun
has burnt off your brain.
- Don't take me for a fool. I'm not one.
- Really?
London was the head of your gang.
This was payback.
You're being childish. You're not smart.
Use your head.
Who killed London?
Eleniyan
Who sent Ify to kill Bolaji the barber?
How do you know about that?
Answer my question.
Eleniyan.
Now we’re getting somewhere.
Let me tell you how it went down.
When we eventually found the barber.
He told us all that happened on that day.
I went to Olorogun and insisted he
sanctioned Kazeem's death.
Olorogun called us to a meeting.
Kazeem said it was London
who drew his gun first.
He said Ifeanyi panicked and shot London.
I knew they were lying.
But it was obvious they had determined
to make Ifeanyi take the fall.
You enemy is closer to you than you know.
You know how these things
happen on the streets.
And eye for an eye.
Blood for blood.
They agreed for Terrible
would kill Ifeanyi.
But if they failed to do so,
we would capture Teni.
Why do you think we let you go that night?
You thought an angel intervened?
Set him free.
When you're ready to take on Kazeem,
I have an army, we'll stand by you.
Understand?
You know I don't like you for shit,
but Kazeem's time is up.
Get up.
Alaye.
Eruku.
I'm sure Ifeanyi would have made it.
He had just recorded a new track
to perform that night.
I can’t believe he’s actually gone.
Omo aiye never brings harm to his own.
But they killed Ify.
What was his crime?
Pana who just wanted to have a good time.
They butchered him
like an animal in the streets.
I know Kazeem is insane,
but not with family.
And that fucking bastard Terrible!
Kazeem is not my family.
I’m going to kill them all.
They broke the rules so all bets are off.
Everyone who cut him,
held him down,
even those that watched.
I'll take revenge.
Even if it costs me my life,
I won’t stop till Kazeem is dead.
Move and I’ll blow your brains off!
What’s the meaning of this?!
How dare you?! Have you gone mad?
Rosy, come and take your money.
You’re part of this? You set me up?
If you want to kill him,
please don’t stain my sheets.
I have another customer coming.
Leave!
You! You set me up.
Help me. Help me!
Open your fucking mouth!
Please don’t kill me.
Please don’t kill me. Please.
Gift says you know where Kazeem
stores his shipment of weapons.
Yes, I know where it is.
It’s across the river.
Shut the fuck up!
Look at him. Fucking bastard!
Come out here!
I'll blow your head off.
Who are you? What do you want...
Oba, what are we waiting for?
Let’s waste this motherfucker.
Wait...
I know something you will want to know.
Oba, this snake is lying.
Terrible, speak, I’m listening.
I need your word you will have
mercy on me when I tell you this.
Oba, if you don’t kill this bastard,
I’ll kill him myself.
Ebun, Stand down.
Terrible, relax, you have my word.
I am sure you've heard the stories
about how loved your father was,
but your father
didn't like Olorogun one bit.
He knew Olorogun wanted to
rule Lagos for his own selfish gains.
So he threw his weight behind
Bamidele's father.
Which Bamidele?
The one running for Governor?
Exactly.
Your father had a lot of influence
and everybody knew Olorogun
was going to lose the election.
That's where Kazeem and Olorogun's
unholy alliance was born.
It was then Olorogun
sent Kazeem to kill your father.
It was a bloodbath.
They killed Bamidele's father,
Ify's father
and anyone else
who was loyal to both of them.
And Alaye Bam Bam?
Who do you think took Kazeem to Olorogun?
For Pana.
Keep it down!
Hello?
Mummy, this is your son…
Oba.
Hello, mummy.
I don’t know that name.
Mummy, it’s Akande.
I said I don’t know who you are.
Mummy, please don’t hang up.
You may never hear my voice again.
Mummy, I know those who killed my father.
I swear I’m going to kill…
Hello Mummy.
Teni!
Traitor!
Your day of reckoning has come.
It’s over.
Drop the gun and fight me like a man.
I don’t need a gun to kill you.
I’ll kill you with my bare hands.
You silly little boy.
You really think you can defeat me.
- You killed my father.
- Your father was a fool.
A fool who wanted to give up everything
so the people would love him.
Well, nobody loves you.
I don't need their love.
I'm a leader.
A leader does what is necessary.
Silly boy.
You don't have what it takes
to seek revenge yet.
You've killed all my loved ones.
All because you want to rule Lagos.
- My son please.
- I'm not your son.
Butcher’s son.
Gangster.
Thug.
Street rat.
There’s nothing I haven’t been called.
Well, this butcher’s son
is going to rule over Lagos.
So it wasn’t London,
it was you who killed Nino.
You’re such a disappointment.
I’ve always thought you had
what it took for greatness.
That you had the courage,
I thought you had plans to be
Eleniyan like me.
But you’re just like your father.
Send my regards when you get to heaven.
Greet them yourself.
Kadara...
Oba.
This is your face.
My Governor.
In nine months.
They can’t stop it.
Not in this lifetime!